■Kigali, Rwanda

inkedIn:https://www.linkedin.com/in/jonathan-kalisa-22756b195/

□GitHub: Jonathan1965

# **KALISA JONATHAN**

# Summary

I Am a Web Developer specializing in front end development and Back end. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP, JAVA, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL, and also I am creative, flexible & able to adapt to changing priorities and maintain a positive and strong work ethic.

#### **CARREER OBJECTIVE**

- To Become a reliable Software engineer who will be able to assist the company or organization towards achieving its mission & goals
- To contribute superior project and operations management skills and experience in an IT management role.
- To utilize my technical skills for achieving the target

# **4** Abilities

#### **AS Web Developer**

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.

#### Education

Bachelor of Science: Adventist University of Central Africa in IT-Networking & Communication System

# **PSkills**

UI/UX Design: Figma, Adobe xd, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator

Programming Skills: HTML5, CSS3, Java, JavaScript, Kotlin

Javascript Framework: Vue and React

PHP Framework: Laravel

CMS: Wordpress & PrestaShop

# ■ Work Experience

#### **Software Eng** - 2015 to 2022

- **Klab** During 2015-2017 I've worked in Klab as a web developer as a part time Job for developing the web projects mentoring kids how to code .
- **Trainer in Nitomani** During A semester in 2016 I Worked in Nitomani School as a gamming programmer with Junior developers to manage the Gaming platform.
- **Trainer in UNESCO AFRICA CODE** During 2017 I worked in UNESCO-Africa Code as a trainer who trained the teachers in Several Station in Rwanda (for three month)
- Coding school program During 2019 I worked in Coding school program where I trained refugees how to code in different programming languages.
- Megus.group worked as UI/UX Design and co-founder in Megus.group and also a COO. I manage the operations and resources of the company.
- Creaxion/TBWA Rwanda During 2018-2021 this was a Product Design Job (UI/UX)job and a Front-end web developer.
- Alight-American refugees committee Am working in ARC as a software Eng Officer am Delved and navigated through unfamiliar codebases, spotted bugs, and proposed fixes.

# Attended Course & Workshop

- Web Development Boot Camp
- Cyber Security In Future Learn
- · Public speaking in Idebate Rwanda
- Cryptocurrency Trading Bot with a User Interface

### Languages

English: Very Good

French: Good

Swahili: Very Good

#### □Links of works Done

- http://connectrwanda.rw/
- http://fzpaintball.rw/
- https://primecementltd.com/
- https://www.rwandair.com/

#### **EREFERENCES**

Mutangana Aphrodice Chief Operations Officer at Digital Africa

amutangana@klab.rw +250 7883 06293.

Mugirase Emanuel CEO at MegusGroup

mugirase@megus.group +250 7822 29462.